popzone.asia 2010-02-23

# popzone.asia | Free Classifieds, Free Ads, Free advertisement, Business Opportunity, Khmer, Cambodia, Asia, Phnom Penh, Directory

**Popzone.asia takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.**

**How Popzone.asia Uses Your Personal Information**

This policy covers how Popzone.asia treats personal information that Popzone.asia collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Popzone.asia products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

**This privacy policy only applies to Popzone.asia**

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Popzone.asia does not own or control or to people that Popzone.asia does not employ or manage.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

Popzone.asia collects personal information when you register with Popzone.asia, when you use Popzone.asia products or services, when you visit Popzone.asia pages or the pages of certain Popzone.asia partners,we may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we might also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. When you register with Popzone.asia and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Popzone.asia collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.

Popzone.asia uses information for the following general purposes to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

Popzone.asia does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Popzone.asia under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Popzone.asia communicate with you about offers from Popzone.asia and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Popzone.asia's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if Popzone.asia is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Popzone.asia will notify you before information about you are transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Popzone.asia does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with. However, by interacting with or viewing an advertisement you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the advertising.

Popzone.asia advertisers include financial service providers and none- financial companies (such as banks, air company, insurance agents, car importer company, real estate company, and other individual company, mini mart stores, airlines, and software companies).

Popzone.asia works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. 

[](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/)**E-mail Communications:** To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from **Popzone.asia** if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please click on **_unsubscribe_**.

**HOW ABOUT THIRD PARTY ADVERTISER AND LINK TO OTHER WEB SITES**

Our site includes third-party advertising and links to other Web sites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party Web sites.    
These third-party Web sites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send and serve the advertisements that appear on our Web site directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertising and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party Web sites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. In addition, the **_network advertising initiative_** offers useful information about Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"), including information about how to opt-out of their information collection.

**Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control:** We work closely with affiliated businesses. In some cases, such as Marketplace sellers, these businesses operate their businesses at Popzone.asia or sell offerings to you at Popzone.asia In other cases; we operate our business, provide services, or sell product lines jointly with these businesses.

**WHAT ABOUT COOKIES**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as, personalized advertisements on other Web sites (e.g., **Popzone.asia** Associates with content served by **Popzone.asia** and Web sites that Popzone.asia using payment service and other related business purpose. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Popzone.asia's essential features, we recommend that you leave them **turned on.**

**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Popzone.asia may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Popzone.asia account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS**

Thanks very much for using our services, if you have any suggestions we love you to contact us by following **_feedback_** Or

**Hot Line : (855)98 598 838 / (855)13 767 746 / (855)17 718 678**

**Customer Care** : E-mail: [_info@popzone.asia_](mailto:info@popzone.asia)

**Advertising Dept** :  E-mail: [_ads@popzone.asia_](mailto:ads@popzone.asia)

**Technical Support:** E-mail: [_support@popzone.asia_](mailto:support@popzone.asia)

**Billing Dept:** E-mail: [_billing@popzone.asia_](mailto:billing@popzone.asia)   

**_(Last up date on June 7, 2009)_**
